(Penny:)Get one yourself.
(Raj:)Ooh, somebody's been
taking bitchy pills.
(Penny:)God, he's an ass when he drinks.
(Howard:)Oh, he's an ass when he doesn't.
(Howard:)You just don't hear it.
(Leonard:)Think we need to start
entertaining the possibility
(Leonard:)that the Shamy could
go on for years.
(Raj:)Well, if that's the case,
Penny will have to get satellite TV
(Raj:)and maybe once a week run a
vacuum through this place.
(Penny:)I thought you were going
to talk to Sheldon.
I did. Well, what'd he say?
(Leonard:)Well, he pointed out that
he kinda sorta had to...
(Leonard:)put up with you.
(Penny:)Kinda sorta had to?
(Leonard:)I didn't agree with him.
(Penny:)Well, you defended me, right?
(Leonard:)I tried, but...
(Leonard:)...he made a fairly
well-reasoned argument.
(Howard:)You're not doing that right.
(Leonard:)What?
(Howard:)Gimme.
No. Trust me.
No! I do this for
my mom all the time.